<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Contribution on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/community-contribution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community Contribution on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/community-contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year In Review</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Looks at dates on blog posts. Oh&amp;hellip;other than my Google Sheets thing, it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip;almost three years since I last posted&amp;hellip;&#xA;Oops. 😅&#xA;What have I been doing in that time? Well&amp;hellip;&#xA;Got A Job&amp;hellip;And Got Laid Off From Said Job In late 2021, I had a full time job opportunity fall into my lap. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of Gun.io since like&amp;hellip;2019 or something like that, back when I first started doing serious freelancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That One Where I Talk For An Hour</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit, I actually just did a talk&amp;hellip;&amp;ldquo;in front of&amp;rdquo; a few hundred people&amp;hellip;for over an hour&amp;hellip; &amp;#x1f631;&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure you, dear reader, fully grasp the gravity of that.&#xA;See, fear of public speaking/stage fright (aka &amp;ldquo;glossophobia&amp;rdquo;) has been a thing that&amp;rsquo;s haunted me for&amp;hellip;basically my entire life. Incessant school bullying and an emotionally abusive head-of-household with a particular enjoyment of telling a 7 year old child everything they did wrong during the school performance, plus dealing with the fallout from a spouse&amp;rsquo;s undiagnosed mental illness will kind of do that to a person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rejection and Mental Health</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>I was turned down for a job today.&#xA;This is nothing new. I&amp;rsquo;ve been turned down for jobs before. Hell, I&amp;rsquo;ve done the job hunt thing on a near-annual basis, which pretty much inevitably results in at least one application rejection per cycle. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many that I&amp;rsquo;ve dealt with such rejections at nearly every step of the process.&#xA;There weren&amp;rsquo;t even a lot of stakes for this job. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking (and was even actively not looking) when it fell into my lap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autism Awareness And The Blue Ranger</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of &amp;ldquo;Autism Awareness Month,&amp;rdquo; which, for those of us with Autism, tends to be &amp;ldquo;the month to run and hide and wish I didn&amp;rsquo;t like blue, because we get inundated with neurotypical people who think they know our experience better than we do.&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t often write about the effect of Autism on my life (either my son&amp;rsquo;s or my own&amp;rsquo;s), because to be honest, 99% of the time, it&amp;rsquo;s boring and uneventful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Keep Going</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</guid>
      <description>When in the throes of a depressive episode (or on the edge of an anxiety attack or any other such motivation killer), it can be hard to maintain motivation and productivity. This can be detrimental when other people rely on you, or when you have a job to hold down.&#xA;Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve found a number of things that have helped keep me motivated through low times, and have decided to share them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Not Alone</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/08/19/youre-not-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/08/19/youre-not-alone/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been torn over how open I should be with this, particularly in my professional life. My first instinct has been for it to be on a very need to know basis.&#xA;Then I met Greg Baugues.&#xA;Greg is a developer evangelist (devangelist) for Twilio, who speaks at conferences about his ADHD and Type II Bipolar, and he gets well-deserved standing ovations pretty much wherever he speaks. I still fight tearing up just thinking about the talk I attended at Laracon, back in mid-May, where he even took his Bipolar medication on stage.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
