<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I make stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My profession is problem solving. My chosen tool by which to do that has been developing software. I&amp;rsquo;ve written shell scripts, maintained systems in .Net, built APIs in PHP, and implemented interfaces with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I&amp;rsquo;ve maintained legacy systems and built cutting-edge, life-changing applications, as well as created little tools to support other people in getting their work done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Writing software isn&amp;rsquo;t all I do, though. I like to write English words, too, and my writing is about as eclectic as my coding. While my blog started (ages ago) as a &amp;ldquo;tech and work blog,&amp;rdquo; it soon expanded out to other aspects of life, including personal finance and the broader culture. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll spin some topics off to their own blogs, eventually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/buy-me-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/buy-me-coffee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;buy-me-coffee&#34;&gt;Buy Me Coffee&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Ways I Make Money From This Site)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-hate-ads&#34;&gt;I &lt;em&gt;Hate&lt;/em&gt; Ads&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do, with a passion. The first extension I install on any browser is AdBlock. That&amp;rsquo;s how much I hate them. I also hate when blogs write a &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo; or other article for the sole purpose of selling that product. You know the kind I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. They read like a commercial and are full of keywords and buzzwords about the product. I can usually spot them a mile away and they annoy the crap out of me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/hire-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/hire-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hiring-me&#34;&gt;Hiring Me&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking to work with me? Cool! Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the type of relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-type&#34;&gt;What Type?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;conventional-employment&#34;&gt;Conventional Employment&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you read through that &amp;#x261d;&amp;#xfe0f; and still want to hire me as a conventional employee? Well&amp;hellip;it didn&amp;rsquo;t scare you away, so that&amp;rsquo;s a start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For my sake and yours, I have a high bar for conventional employment in particular. Let&amp;rsquo;s put it this way: I&amp;rsquo;ve turned down Amazon roughly half a dozen times at this point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventures in Modernizing React</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/09/08/adventures-in-modernizing-react/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/09/08/adventures-in-modernizing-react/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent the better part of my first year at Custom Ink upgrading an Electron and React application. That was an adventure unto itself, let me tell you. It also resulted in a list of &amp;ldquo;things I need to do when my priority isn&amp;rsquo;t just get this thing working again to unblock the other team.&amp;rdquo; Among that list was updating the code to modern standards &amp;ndash; something I got to make a bunch of headway on in the second half of my second year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open 3D Engine</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/05/13/open-3d-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/05/13/open-3d-engine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting a new gig is very often described as &amp;ldquo;drinking from the fire hose,&amp;rdquo; and for good reason &amp;ndash; the primary job for a new person for the first few months is simply taking in everything about the job, the work, the people, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have proceeded to jack that up to eleven.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Why get just a new job, when I can get a new job, in an industry I&amp;rsquo;ve never worked in, working in a language I&amp;rsquo;ve never touched?!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Companies are not family</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/27/companies-are-not-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/27/companies-are-not-family/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re a family here!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How many times have you heard that from your boss? Or perhaps even the CEO of your company? I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it at nearly every company I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for. And I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;its-a-trap&#34;&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s A Trap&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/images/bait-thats-bait.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Tom Hardy in Mad Max shaking his head no, &amp;ldquo;that&amp;rsquo;s bait&amp;rdquo;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(I considered the &lt;em&gt;Star Wars&lt;/em&gt; meme, but I like this one better.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What do you call a familial relationship in which one person controls another&amp;rsquo;s financial security in order to gain compliance?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year In Review</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Looks at dates on blog posts.&lt;/em&gt; Oh&amp;hellip;other than my Google Sheets thing, it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip;almost three years since I last posted&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oops. 😅&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What have I been doing in that time? Well&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;got-a-joband-got-laid-off-from-said-job&#34;&gt;Got A Job&amp;hellip;And Got Laid Off From Said Job&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In late 2021, I had a full time job opportunity fall into my lap. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of &lt;a href=&#34;https://gun.io&#34;&gt;Gun.io&lt;/a&gt; since like&amp;hellip;2019 or something like that, back when I first started doing serious freelancing. Sometime during 2021, they started offering more full-time positions, and the account manager there sent me a message about one at a little (&amp;ldquo;little&amp;rdquo;) company called Custom Ink.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fixing The Google Sheets View Only Bug</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2023/11/17/fixing-the-google-sheets-view-only-bug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2023/11/17/fixing-the-google-sheets-view-only-bug/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have you ever been using Google Sheets on your Android or iPhone, then suddenly find a sheet that you own stuck in read only mode? Or maybe you opened it to find a message that says &amp;ldquo;this document has changed significantly. Reload to sync,&amp;rdquo; and then it goes read only?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have. It&amp;rsquo;s annoying as hell, and made yet more annoying by the fact that not a single help forum seems to acknowledge this is even an issue! I have found some half a dozen posts dating back to 2019 with the same symptoms and the same brain-dead &amp;ldquo;answers&amp;rdquo; and &lt;em&gt;none&lt;/em&gt; of them actually fix the problem!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>That One Where I Talk For An Hour</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Holy shit, I &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; just did a talk&amp;hellip;&amp;ldquo;in front of&amp;rdquo; a few hundred people&amp;hellip;for over an hour&amp;hellip; &amp;#x1f631;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure you, dear reader, fully grasp the gravity of that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See, fear of public speaking/stage fright (aka &amp;ldquo;glossophobia&amp;rdquo;) has been a thing that&amp;rsquo;s haunted me for&amp;hellip;basically my entire life. Incessant school bullying and an emotionally abusive head-of-household with a particular enjoyment of telling a 7 year old child everything they did wrong during the school performance, plus dealing with the fallout from a spouse&amp;rsquo;s undiagnosed mental illness will kind of do that to a person.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Look Back At Shipt</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/10/a-look-back-at-shipt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/10/a-look-back-at-shipt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I happened to notice the other day that my site gets a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; more traffic than I realized (thanks, PointHQ!), so I tossed a little, lightweight analytics thing onto it so I can see where people are going and maybe we&amp;rsquo;re they&amp;rsquo;re coming from. (Hi, people! &amp;#x1f44b;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the things I noticed was that &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/a-week-of-shipt&#34;&gt;an old, &lt;em&gt;old&lt;/em&gt; blog post&lt;/a&gt; of mine was getting hit. Like&amp;hellip;so old that I didn&amp;rsquo;t migrate it originally, considering it defunct and no longer applicable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Problem Solving</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/10/21/on-problem-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/10/21/on-problem-solving/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The most important skill in tech isn&amp;rsquo;t the technology. It&amp;rsquo;s problem-solving. Whether you get into cyber security, system administration, or programming, the heart of all of it is really the ability to take a problem, break it apart, and work out a solution &amp;ndash; very often coming up with solutions that didn&amp;rsquo;t previously exist at all. Even on the more everyday scale, you&amp;rsquo;ll be constantly faced with error messages, odd software behavior, broken tests, and more that you&amp;rsquo;ll be expected to triage and if not fix yourself, hand off detailed information about the problem to those who can fix it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rejection and Mental Health</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was turned down for a job today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is nothing new. I&amp;rsquo;ve been turned down for jobs before. Hell, I&amp;rsquo;ve done the job hunt thing on a near-annual basis, which pretty much inevitably results in at least one application rejection per cycle. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many that I&amp;rsquo;ve dealt with such rejections at nearly every step of the process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There weren&amp;rsquo;t even a lot of stakes for this job. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking (and was even actively &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; looking) when it fell into my lap. I didn&amp;rsquo;t even &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; the job (which changed the entire feel of the interviews even more than I anticipated).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What We Owe To Each Other</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The topic of changing verbiage within the tech industry, particularly as it relates to references to &amp;ldquo;master,&amp;rdquo; particularly in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; contexts, but also in places like &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch in git (which does, in fact, &lt;a href=&#34;https://mail.gnome.org/archives/desktop-devel-list/2019-May/msg00066.html&#34;&gt;have its roots in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; paradigm&lt;/a&gt;), came up in a couple of Slack groups in which I participate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s certainly not new (some discussions on the matter date back a decade or more), but it&amp;rsquo;s always kind of a contentious topic when it comes up, despite the terminology getting phased out over time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riot Is the Language of the Unheard</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I attended a protest the other day. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d been downtown since it started and I had walked there (and back) from one of the suburbs. A nearly 5 mile walk each way, with the inner-most mile or two containing a lot of plywood covering up a lot of damage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But you know what stuck out to me? Two things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which places were hit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Of the places that were damaged and thus boarded up, which had murals and which had graffiti.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These two things speak volumes about the situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventures In A Remote World</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/05/03/adventures-in-a-remote-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/05/03/adventures-in-a-remote-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Among my many blog post drafts, I have a satirical piece that was originally intended to turn all the &amp;ldquo;remote working is inferior [because it&amp;rsquo;s a new thing with a learning curve]&amp;rdquo; stuff on its head.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;And then COVID-19 happened and pretty much overnight, just about everyone suddenly had to do at least some things remotely (even if work wasn&amp;rsquo;t one of them).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Schools are all now done in distance learning format (hat-tip to all of the school staff who busted their tails to make that pivot and get students of all ages going with relatively little disruption!). Zoom, Hangouts, and all the other video conference services are flooded with new people setting up every meeting, conference, non-meeting gathering, meetup, and social time under the sun. ISPs are getting bitch-slapped for not maintaining or upgrading their last-mile lines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pandemic Work From Home Survival Guide</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/03/16/the-pandemic-work-from-home-survival-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/03/16/the-pandemic-work-from-home-survival-guide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some Notes:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Contrary to most of my other posts, I plan to update this one periodically as things change and this is still current. Check back periodically for updates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are you a business owner or manager? Have a look at &lt;a href=&#34;https://remotewave.io/blog/the-emergency-remote-work-guide/&#34;&gt;Remotewave.io&amp;rsquo;s guide,&lt;/a&gt; which approaches it from your side. :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well&amp;hellip;now that half the world is in quarantine of some level, a great many people are suddenly finding themselves tossed head first in the deep end of remote working. Odds are pretty good neither them nor their employers are really prepared for this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Platform</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/15/new-blog-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:02:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/15/new-blog-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip;Pelican (my previous static site generator) took a dump on me when I went to upload my latest blog post&amp;hellip; I attempted multiple paths to resurrect it, but they&amp;rsquo;ve all ultimately failed. &amp;#x1f622;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a result, I&amp;rsquo;m moving my site to Hugo, but that requires some conversion (and probably clean-up). It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit tedious, but it does mean I&amp;rsquo;ve cleaned up my &lt;em&gt;ancient&lt;/em&gt; posts that are no longer relevant, which is a plus. It also means there might be some minor bugs or other things in need of tweaking, though, and possibly a couple of dead links. I think I got the important ones, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Q4 2018 Update</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/13/personal-finance-q4-2018-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/13/personal-finance-q4-2018-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I actually had another installment of this series written back in February or so. I ended up scrapping it when life rendered it completely wrong almost as soon as I&amp;rsquo;d finished writing it. &amp;#x1f926;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember in &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/23/personal-finance-part-3/&#34;&gt;part 3&lt;/a&gt;, where I mentioned that I got my windows replaced?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Apparently such investments have side-effects&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;maybe-i-should-start-a-lemon-orchard&#34;&gt;Maybe I Should Start A Lemon Orchard&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;hellip;Like frying the HVAC system, because it&amp;rsquo;s oversized for the house, when said house is properly insulated. Nothing like spending a hot, rainy summer in a house with crap natural airflow, without air conditioning.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autism Awareness And The Blue Ranger</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s the start of &amp;ldquo;Autism Awareness Month,&amp;rdquo; which, for those of us &lt;em&gt;with&lt;/em&gt; Autism, tends to be &amp;ldquo;the month to run and hide and wish I didn&amp;rsquo;t like blue, because we get inundated with neurotypical people who think they know our experience better than we do.&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t often write about the effect of Autism on my life (either my son&amp;rsquo;s or my own&amp;rsquo;s), because to be honest, 99% of the time, it&amp;rsquo;s boring and uneventful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Core Values</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I&amp;rsquo;ve more actively sought out leadership positions, one of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about is the concept of core values. I see them actually communicated most often at the organization level, but I believe we have them at a personal level, too. We just don&amp;rsquo;t codify them. I like documenting things (because I like understanding), and since these are things I&amp;rsquo;d like to instill in the people I mentor and lead, I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be good to write them out and start documenting and exploring, and ultimately refining them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, I wrote a post on &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/&#34;&gt;automating the generation of my static-site blog&lt;/a&gt;. As they do, things have since changed, and I figured I&amp;rsquo;d update accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;changes-to-travis-and-travisyml&#34;&gt;Changes To Travis And .travis.yml&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Travis recently made several updates, many of which make our job easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;build-settings&#34;&gt;Build Settings&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Travis now has the option to build only if a .travis.yml file is present. Before, you needed a .travis.yml file in both your source and your display branch. Now, that&amp;rsquo;s no longer the case.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shopify HMAC Verification</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/24/shopify-hmac-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 01:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/24/shopify-hmac-verification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote class=&#34;alert alert-important&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;alert-heading&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;strong&gt;&#xA;        ℹ️&#xA;        &#xA;          Important&#xA;        &#xA;        &lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;If the date doesn&amp;rsquo;t make it evident, this is an old post. In the intervening years, Shopify has made a lot of changes, including a recent heavy overhaul. I&amp;rsquo;m leaving this up for posterity, but I don&amp;rsquo;t know or guarantee that it still works in light of those changes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;I get the pleasure of writing integration after integration to Shopify at my day job. As a result, I have become quite familiar with their documentation and its gaps. The HMAC verification piece of the OAuth/embedded app installation process is a particularly glaring gap. So let&amp;rsquo;s close it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Part 3</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/23/personal-finance-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/23/personal-finance-part-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2016/12/16/personal-finance-part-2/&#34;&gt;part 2&lt;/a&gt;, I mentioned that I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;productively lazy,&amp;rdquo; and prefer to automate what I can. Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to do that with my finances.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;hello-automation&#34;&gt;Hello, Automation!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My husband finally got officially hired by his work, which converted him to salary. This gave us two benefits &amp;ndash; 1. his income is no longer locked to his hours, so the paychecks are the same, and 2. he and I are now on the same pay schedule (which makes for a really pretty number on payday).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/12/16/personal-finance-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/12/16/personal-finance-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Back in &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/04/getting-started-with-personal-finance/&#34;&gt;part 1&lt;/a&gt; I described the system that I used to work on getting my family out of debt and make ends meet. We&amp;rsquo;re now coming up on a year, so how did I do? Does this system actually work?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;putting-the-system-to-work&#34;&gt;Putting The System To Work&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, did it work? Well, as an acquaintance put it, there was &amp;ldquo;no budge in the budget,&amp;rdquo; but&amp;hellip;yeah, it has been working. In fact, it saved our hides when things fell apart a few months ago. I did tweak a few things, though.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Public Speaking And Self Esteem</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/06/29/on-public-speaking-and-self-esteem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/06/29/on-public-speaking-and-self-esteem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I got an invite from Cal Evans to watch this week&amp;rsquo;s episode of his weekly show, with this week&amp;rsquo;s topic being a public speaking Q&amp;amp;A with Adam Culp (as this is the &lt;em&gt;third&lt;/em&gt; time Cal has pinged me regarding public speaking, I think he &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wants me to start &amp;#x1f62e;). It got me thinking again about my feelings toward the prospect of public speaking for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Espeically when it&amp;rsquo;s for larger audiences, my knee-jerk response to &amp;ldquo;you should give a talk,&amp;rdquo; has historically been &amp;ldquo;hell no.&amp;rdquo; For the longest time, I chalked it up to glossophobia (aka - stage fright/fear of public speaking). Recently, though, things in my life have changed such that the idea is no longer so panic-inducing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being A Shiptster, Three Months In</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/18/being-a-shiptster-three-months-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/18/being-a-shiptster-three-months-in/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, three months have passed since &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.shipt.com/&#34;&gt;Shipt&lt;/a&gt; launched. So, how is it going?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well&amp;hellip; these Facebook posts are rather indicative:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/plugins/post.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2FShipttoday%2Fposts%2F541092312740359&amp;width=500&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;180&#34; style=&#34;border:none;overflow:hidden&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowTransparency=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/plugins/post.php?href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2FShipttoday%2Fposts%2F540685849447672&amp;width=500&#34; width=&#34;500&#34; height=&#34;161&#34; style=&#34;border:none;overflow:hidden&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowTransparency=&#34;true&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-happened&#34;&gt;What Happened?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, they recently made a change to their algorithm for order offers, which has greatly upset a great number of the shoppers and even for those that aren&amp;rsquo;t upset, it has altered how people schedule. Some people have removed themselves from the schedule out of protest, while others have done so out of necessity, so that their ranking isn&amp;rsquo;t affected by missing offers while working at another job.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Personal Finance</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/04/getting-started-with-personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/04/getting-started-with-personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I could have sworn I wrote earlier about how one of the things I was planning on doing was personal finance and money-making outside of a typical 9-5. Oh well, if I haven&amp;rsquo;t said it before, I&amp;rsquo;ll say it now &amp;ndash; I find it annoying that there seems to be a gap between &amp;ldquo;flat broke with zero personal finance knowledge&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;personal finance guru,&amp;rdquo; and I&amp;rsquo;d like to bridge that gap, while I&amp;rsquo;m crossing it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Week Of Shipt</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/a-week-of-shipt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/a-week-of-shipt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hey-o! This is a really old post and no longer reflects what I do. I ended up going back to software development in October of that year. It was a nice break, but unfortunately, 2016 was also the year gig economy jobs as a whole kind of took a dump. This is here for posterity, though, to avoid broken links. Be sure to &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/10/a-look-back-at-shipt&#34;&gt;read the update&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/JzuCGI5.gif&#34; alt=&#34;The grocery deliverator from Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs 2. A young man throws produce into a portal and the produce comes out another portal onto his father&amp;rsquo;s head.&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hey-o! There have been some changes made to this process. &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github&#34;&gt;Be sure to check out the updates.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is actually the second time I&amp;rsquo;ve leveraged &lt;a href=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/&#34;&gt;Travis CI&lt;/a&gt; for managing my static-site blog, but apparently I didn&amp;rsquo;t write about it. I had done it shortly after setting up the Octopress version of my blog. It was nice and convenient, and dramatically lowered the barrier to writing more blog entries, though I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that until I lost that capability when I switched to Pelican (probably because the Octopress version was a bit finicky, due to breaking changes in the upstream Octopress repo, so the barrier was still pretty high).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding One&#39;s Strengths</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;whats-this-strengths-finding-thing&#34;&gt;What&amp;rsquo;s This Strengths Finding Thing?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to a lot of podcasts lately. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly a fan of &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.smartpassiveincome.com/&#34;&gt;Smart Passive Income&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;http://screwtheninetofive.com/&#34;&gt;Screw The Nine To Five&lt;/a&gt;. They&amp;rsquo;re both great podcasts for learning about how to build your own business in order to generate income that&amp;rsquo;s not dependent on trading your time for money. They&amp;rsquo;re a gold mine of various resources, not just for starting and running one&amp;rsquo;s own business, but for business and life stuff in general.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Developer to Shipt Shopper</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/from-developer-to-shipt-shopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/from-developer-to-shipt-shopper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wait&amp;hellip;what? I traded a lucrative programming career for&amp;hellip;buying and delivering groceries?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In short, yes. For now, at least.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;simply-put----i-got-burned-the-f---out&#34;&gt;Simply Put &amp;ndash; I Got Burned The F&amp;ndash; Out&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I left my development job just before Thanksgiving. I all but literally told them &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not you, it&amp;rsquo;s me,&amp;rdquo; because that was the truth. I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything but good stuff to say about the company I worked for, because they were about as close to perfect as I&amp;rsquo;ve found. They really didn&amp;rsquo;t care about the number of hours you worked, as long as you got the work done. They care about their employees (I went to the upper management a couple of times with some issues, and not only did they &lt;em&gt;listen&lt;/em&gt; to what I had to say, they took it seriously and made change in order to fix the underlying problem). They valued employees&amp;rsquo; time and acted accordingly (kept meetings and interruptions to a minimum, had an unlimited paid time off policy, etc). The code, itself, is what burnt me out, really, and even that, had I been able to stick it out, probably would have resolved over time, as we modernized the legacy system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Culture Trumps Everything</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/15/when-culture-trumps-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/15/when-culture-trumps-everything/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I had an interesting experience recently.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I had a job opportunity dropped in my lap. A greenfield project that had a pay range $10-40k more than what I&amp;rsquo;m currently making.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have my attention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I responded to the recruiter and within a few days, I had an initial meeting/interview with one of the higher-ups at the company.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I went and had a nice conversation with him. He was a cool person, not much older than myself. The company itself was pretty cool, and looked and acted very much like a Silicon Valley startup. We even sat in a conference room that had a feminism-themed mural on one wall (I was told that each of the conference rooms had mural of different themes, though the other rooms were occupied at the time, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t get to see much of them). The primary working space sported a handful of colorful market umbrellas (which I later found out served the purpose of shielding some of the employees from the direct sunlight that streamed in from the skylights overhead) interspersed through the three columns of desks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exchange With Amazon On Workplace Culture</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of months ago, I got an invitation to an Amazon recruiting event:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;Hi Shauna-&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;I came across your information in our system and your background is impressive! We are currently looking to hire Sr. Software Development Engineers (SDEs) to join the Amazon Retail team and are hosting an “Invitation Only” recruiting event for the Amazon Media and International Expansion (ISE) organizations specifically the week of February 16th.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;    &lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;If you’re interested in being considered for this opportunity, please reply with your updated resume to [Recruiter&amp;rsquo;s email] if you’d like to be considered. Once we receive your response, we will evaluate your candidacy for consideration for the event.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Remote Friendly Work Environments</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/05/15/in-defense-of-remote-friendly-work-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/05/15/in-defense-of-remote-friendly-work-environments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since I posted my &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/15/dear-recruiters/&#34;&gt;open letter to recruiters&lt;/a&gt;, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a number of people speaking out against it (&amp;ldquo;against&amp;rdquo; used loosely here, ranging from &amp;ldquo;employees &lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt; to be in the office&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;the best companies hire the best people and the best people &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; to go into the office&amp;rdquo; (that&amp;rsquo;s not insulting &lt;em&gt;at all&lt;/em&gt;) to &amp;ldquo;working remotely is isolating&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;in-person communication is better&amp;rdquo;). I decided to address a few of these things head-on.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Keep Going</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When in the throes of a depressive episode (or on the edge of an anxiety attack or any other such motivation killer), it can be hard to maintain motivation and productivity. This can be detrimental when other people rely on you, or when you have a job to hold down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve found a number of things that have helped keep me motivated through low times, and have decided to share them. Unlike other articles giving advice on &amp;ldquo;cheering up,&amp;rdquo; the items here may or may not actually lift your mood. That&amp;rsquo;s not the point of them, and anyone who&amp;rsquo;s dealt with depression will tell you that most of the time, things designed to &amp;ldquo;cheer you up&amp;rdquo; don&amp;rsquo;t really work. If it does lift your mood, then that&amp;rsquo;s a positive side effect, but as Winston Churchill put it, &amp;ldquo;when you&amp;rsquo;re going through hell, keep going.&amp;rdquo; These items are intended to do &lt;em&gt;that&lt;/em&gt; &amp;ndash; help you keep going.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Letter To Recruiters</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/15/dear-recruiters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/15/dear-recruiters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Dear Third Party Recruiters,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to the high volume of contact requests I’ve received, I have decided to write this open letter in order to improve the quality of my network.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Greater Columbus Area is home to a very large number of third party recruiting companies. This means &lt;strong&gt;you have a lot of competition&lt;/strong&gt;. Competition should mean improved quality. Unfortunately, what I generally see is rather disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We tech folks are generally a merit-based people. We’ll respect you if we have reason to do so. You can earn that respect by demonstrating that you respect us and what we do (and no, saying that you do doesn’t cut it; show, don’t tell). Here are some ways to do that.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;re Not Alone</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/08/19/youre-not-alone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/08/19/youre-not-alone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been torn over how open I should be with this, particularly in my professional life. My first instinct has been for it to be on a very need to know basis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then I met &lt;a href=&#34;http://baugues.com/&#34;&gt;Greg Baugues&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Greg is a developer evangelist (devangelist) for &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.twilio.com/&#34;&gt;Twilio&lt;/a&gt;, who speaks at conferences about his ADHD and Type II Bipolar, and he gets well-deserved standing ovations pretty much wherever he speaks. I still fight tearing up just thinking about &lt;a href=&#34;http://userscape.com/laracon/2014/gregbaugues.html&#34;&gt;the talk I attended at Laracon&lt;/a&gt;, back in mid-May, where he even took his Bipolar medication on stage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Handcrafted CSS</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/06/21/review-handcrafted-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/06/21/review-handcrafted-css/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#39;post&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0321658531?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0321658531&#34;&gt;Handcrafted CSS: More Bulletproof Web Design, Video Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.assoc-amazon.com/e/ir?t=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=0321658531&#34; width=&#34;1&#34; height=&#34;1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While at one of my previous clients, a coworker ordered this book as a resource at the office. I was the first to read it and simply couldn&#39;t put it down. &lt;em&gt;Handcrafted CSS: More Bulletproof Web Design&lt;/em&gt; highlights modern CSS techniques that help build robust, attractive, designs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;!-- more --&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike most technical books, which often provide too much tech and not enough explanation, or too much theory and not enough tech, this book provides a fantastic balance, and even uses a running case study that it builds and enhances as the reader progresses through the book. Not only are readers able to understand the concepts the book presents, but they also learn ways to put the new concepts into practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Why Work Sucks (And How to Fix It)</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/05/16/review-why-work-sucks-and-how-to-fix-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/05/16/review-why-work-sucks-and-how-to-fix-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#39;post&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B001OMHV0K?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B001OMHV0K&#34;&gt;Why Work Sucks and How to Fix It: No Schedules, No Meetings, No Joke--the Simple Change That Can Make Your Job Terrific&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.assoc-amazon.com/e/ir?t=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=B001OMHV0K&#34; width=&#34;1&#34; height=&#34;1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You anxiously look at your watch as the traffic creeps forward - 8:55am. There&#39;s no way you&#39;ll get to the office by 9, you still have 10 miles to go. When you finally do arrive at 9:15, you try to sneak to your desk unnoticed, but your boss is already there. &#34;So nice of you to join us this morning,&#34; he greets you, a &#34;do it again and you&#39;re fired&#34; look on his face. You sit down at your desk, still a little too agitated to start work quite yet, so you read your favorite news site for ten minutes. Part of you resigns to this life, believing it&#39;s the way things are, and nothing will change, but another part of you feels that there must be a better way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
