<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Review on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/review/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Review on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Review: Handcrafted CSS</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/06/21/review-handcrafted-css/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/06/21/review-handcrafted-css/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#39;post&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0321658531?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=0321658531&#34;&gt;Handcrafted CSS: More Bulletproof Web Design, Video Edition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.assoc-amazon.com/e/ir?t=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=0321658531&#34; width=&#34;1&#34; height=&#34;1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While at one of my previous clients, a coworker ordered this book as a resource at the office. I was the first to read it and simply couldn&#39;t put it down. &lt;em&gt;Handcrafted CSS: More Bulletproof Web Design&lt;/em&gt; highlights modern CSS techniques that help build robust, attractive, designs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;!-- more --&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike most technical books, which often provide too much tech and not enough explanation, or too much theory and not enough tech, this book provides a fantastic balance, and even uses a running case study that it builds and enhances as the reader progresses through the book. Not only are readers able to understand the concepts the book presents, but they also learn ways to put the new concepts into practice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Review: Why Work Sucks (And How to Fix It)</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/05/16/review-why-work-sucks-and-how-to-fix-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 May 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2010/05/16/review-why-work-sucks-and-how-to-fix-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#39;post&#39;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B001OMHV0K?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B001OMHV0K&#34;&gt;Why Work Sucks and How to Fix It: No Schedules, No Meetings, No Joke--the Simple Change That Can Make Your Job Terrific&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.assoc-amazon.com/e/ir?t=graywolfweb-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=B001OMHV0K&#34; width=&#34;1&#34; height=&#34;1&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You anxiously look at your watch as the traffic creeps forward - 8:55am. There&#39;s no way you&#39;ll get to the office by 9, you still have 10 miles to go. When you finally do arrive at 9:15, you try to sneak to your desk unnoticed, but your boss is already there. &#34;So nice of you to join us this morning,&#34; he greets you, a &#34;do it again and you&#39;re fired&#34; look on his face. You sit down at your desk, still a little too agitated to start work quite yet, so you read your favorite news site for ten minutes. Part of you resigns to this life, believing it&#39;s the way things are, and nothing will change, but another part of you feels that there must be a better way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
