<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Community on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/categories/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/categories/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>That One Where I Talk For An Hour</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/11/that-one-where-i-talk-for-an-hour/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit, I actually just did a talk&amp;hellip;&amp;ldquo;in front of&amp;rdquo; a few hundred people&amp;hellip;for over an hour&amp;hellip; &amp;#x1f631;&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure you, dear reader, fully grasp the gravity of that.&#xA;See, fear of public speaking/stage fright (aka &amp;ldquo;glossophobia&amp;rdquo;) has been a thing that&amp;rsquo;s haunted me for&amp;hellip;basically my entire life. Incessant school bullying and an emotionally abusive head-of-household with a particular enjoyment of telling a 7 year old child everything they did wrong during the school performance, plus dealing with the fallout from a spouse&amp;rsquo;s undiagnosed mental illness will kind of do that to a person.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rejection and Mental Health</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>I was turned down for a job today.&#xA;This is nothing new. I&amp;rsquo;ve been turned down for jobs before. Hell, I&amp;rsquo;ve done the job hunt thing on a near-annual basis, which pretty much inevitably results in at least one application rejection per cycle. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many that I&amp;rsquo;ve dealt with such rejections at nearly every step of the process.&#xA;There weren&amp;rsquo;t even a lot of stakes for this job. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking (and was even actively not looking) when it fell into my lap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What We Owe To Each Other</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</guid>
      <description>The topic of changing verbiage within the tech industry, particularly as it relates to references to &amp;ldquo;master,&amp;rdquo; particularly in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; contexts, but also in places like &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch in git (which does, in fact, have its roots in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; paradigm), came up in a couple of Slack groups in which I participate.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s certainly not new (some discussions on the matter date back a decade or more), but it&amp;rsquo;s always kind of a contentious topic when it comes up, despite the terminology getting phased out over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riot Is the Language of the Unheard</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</guid>
      <description>So I attended a protest the other day. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d been downtown since it started and I had walked there (and back) from one of the suburbs. A nearly 5 mile walk each way, with the inner-most mile or two containing a lot of plywood covering up a lot of damage.&#xA;But you know what stuck out to me? Two things:&#xA;Which places were hit. Of the places that were damaged and thus boarded up, which had murals and which had graffiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Autism Awareness And The Blue Ranger</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2018 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/04/01/autism-awareness-and-the-blue-ranger/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s the start of &amp;ldquo;Autism Awareness Month,&amp;rdquo; which, for those of us with Autism, tends to be &amp;ldquo;the month to run and hide and wish I didn&amp;rsquo;t like blue, because we get inundated with neurotypical people who think they know our experience better than we do.&amp;rdquo; I don&amp;rsquo;t often write about the effect of Autism on my life (either my son&amp;rsquo;s or my own&amp;rsquo;s), because to be honest, 99% of the time, it&amp;rsquo;s boring and uneventful.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
