<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mental Health on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/mental-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mental Health on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/mental-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year In Review</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Looks at dates on blog posts. Oh&amp;hellip;other than my Google Sheets thing, it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip;almost three years since I last posted&amp;hellip;&#xA;Oops. 😅&#xA;What have I been doing in that time? Well&amp;hellip;&#xA;Got A Job&amp;hellip;And Got Laid Off From Said Job In late 2021, I had a full time job opportunity fall into my lap. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of Gun.io since like&amp;hellip;2019 or something like that, back when I first started doing serious freelancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Rejection and Mental Health</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/09/04/on-rejection-and-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>I was turned down for a job today.&#xA;This is nothing new. I&amp;rsquo;ve been turned down for jobs before. Hell, I&amp;rsquo;ve done the job hunt thing on a near-annual basis, which pretty much inevitably results in at least one application rejection per cycle. I&amp;rsquo;ve had so many that I&amp;rsquo;ve dealt with such rejections at nearly every step of the process.&#xA;There weren&amp;rsquo;t even a lot of stakes for this job. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t looking (and was even actively not looking) when it fell into my lap.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ways To Keep Going</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/30/motivation/</guid>
      <description>When in the throes of a depressive episode (or on the edge of an anxiety attack or any other such motivation killer), it can be hard to maintain motivation and productivity. This can be detrimental when other people rely on you, or when you have a job to hold down.&#xA;Over the years, I&amp;rsquo;ve found a number of things that have helped keep me motivated through low times, and have decided to share them.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
