<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>shipt on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/shipt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in shipt on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/shipt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Look Back At Shipt</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/10/a-look-back-at-shipt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2021/02/10/a-look-back-at-shipt/</guid>
      <description>So I happened to notice the other day that my site gets a lot more traffic than I realized (thanks, PointHQ!), so I tossed a little, lightweight analytics thing onto it so I can see where people are going and maybe we&amp;rsquo;re they&amp;rsquo;re coming from. (Hi, people! &amp;#x1f44b;)&#xA;One of the things I noticed was that an old, old blog post of mine was getting hit. Like&amp;hellip;so old that I didn&amp;rsquo;t migrate it originally, considering it defunct and no longer applicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being A Shiptster, Three Months In</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/18/being-a-shiptster-three-months-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/18/being-a-shiptster-three-months-in/</guid>
      <description>So, three months have passed since Shipt launched. So, how is it going?&#xA;Well&amp;hellip; these Facebook posts are rather indicative:&#xA;What Happened? Well, they recently made a change to their algorithm for order offers, which has greatly upset a great number of the shoppers and even for those that aren&amp;rsquo;t upset, it has altered how people schedule. Some people have removed themselves from the schedule out of protest, while others have done so out of necessity, so that their ranking isn&amp;rsquo;t affected by missing offers while working at another job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Week Of Shipt</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/a-week-of-shipt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/a-week-of-shipt/</guid>
      <description>Hey-o! This is a really old post and no longer reflects what I do. I ended up going back to software development in October of that year. It was a nice break, but unfortunately, 2016 was also the year gig economy jobs as a whole kind of took a dump. This is here for posterity, though, to avoid broken links. Be sure to read the update&#xA;Yes, this is basically what I do, minus the mess.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Developer to Shipt Shopper</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/from-developer-to-shipt-shopper/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/from-developer-to-shipt-shopper/</guid>
      <description>Wait&amp;hellip;what? I traded a lucrative programming career for&amp;hellip;buying and delivering groceries?&#xA;In short, yes. For now, at least.&#xA;Simply Put &amp;ndash; I Got Burned The F&amp;ndash; Out I left my development job just before Thanksgiving. I all but literally told them &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not you, it&amp;rsquo;s me,&amp;rdquo; because that was the truth. I don&amp;rsquo;t have anything but good stuff to say about the company I worked for, because they were about as close to perfect as I&amp;rsquo;ve found.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
