<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diversity on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/diversity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Diversity on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/diversity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What We Owe To Each Other</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</guid>
      <description>The topic of changing verbiage within the tech industry, particularly as it relates to references to &amp;ldquo;master,&amp;rdquo; particularly in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; contexts, but also in places like &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch in git (which does, in fact, have its roots in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; paradigm), came up in a couple of Slack groups in which I participate.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s certainly not new (some discussions on the matter date back a decade or more), but it&amp;rsquo;s always kind of a contentious topic when it comes up, despite the terminology getting phased out over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riot Is the Language of the Unheard</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</guid>
      <description>So I attended a protest the other day. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d been downtown since it started and I had walked there (and back) from one of the suburbs. A nearly 5 mile walk each way, with the inner-most mile or two containing a lot of plywood covering up a lot of damage.&#xA;But you know what stuck out to me? Two things:&#xA;Which places were hit. Of the places that were damaged and thus boarded up, which had murals and which had graffiti.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding One&#39;s Strengths</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s This Strengths Finding Thing? I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to a lot of podcasts lately. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly a fan of Smart Passive Income and Screw The Nine To Five. They&amp;rsquo;re both great podcasts for learning about how to build your own business in order to generate income that&amp;rsquo;s not dependent on trading your time for money. They&amp;rsquo;re a gold mine of various resources, not just for starting and running one&amp;rsquo;s own business, but for business and life stuff in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exchange With Amazon On Workplace Culture</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I got an invitation to an Amazon recruiting event:&#xA;Hi Shauna-&#xA;I came across your information in our system and your background is impressive! We are currently looking to hire Sr. Software Development Engineers (SDEs) to join the Amazon Retail team and are hosting an “Invitation Only” recruiting event for the Amazon Media and International Expansion (ISE) organizations specifically the week of February 16th.&#xA;If you’re interested in being considered for this opportunity, please reply with your updated resume to [Recruiter&amp;rsquo;s email] if you’d like to be considered.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
