<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Automation on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Automation on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 23:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Last year, I wrote a post on automating the generation of my static-site blog. As they do, things have since changed, and I figured I&amp;rsquo;d update accordingly.&#xA;Changes To Travis And .travis.yml Travis recently made several updates, many of which make our job easier.&#xA;Build Settings Travis now has the option to build only if a .travis.yml file is present. Before, you needed a .travis.yml file in both your source and your display branch.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</guid>
      <description>Hey-o! There have been some changes made to this process. Be sure to check out the updates.&#xA;This is actually the second time I&amp;rsquo;ve leveraged Travis CI for managing my static-site blog, but apparently I didn&amp;rsquo;t write about it. I had done it shortly after setting up the Octopress version of my blog. It was nice and convenient, and dramatically lowered the barrier to writing more blog entries, though I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that until I lost that capability when I switched to Pelican (probably because the Octopress version was a bit finicky, due to breaking changes in the upstream Octopress repo, so the barrier was still pretty high).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
