<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Debt on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/debt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Debt on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/debt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year In Review</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Looks at dates on blog posts. Oh&amp;hellip;other than my Google Sheets thing, it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip;almost three years since I last posted&amp;hellip;&#xA;Oops. 😅&#xA;What have I been doing in that time? Well&amp;hellip;&#xA;Got A Job&amp;hellip;And Got Laid Off From Said Job In late 2021, I had a full time job opportunity fall into my lap. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of Gun.io since like&amp;hellip;2019 or something like that, back when I first started doing serious freelancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Q4 2018 Update</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/13/personal-finance-q4-2018-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/13/personal-finance-q4-2018-update/</guid>
      <description>I actually had another installment of this series written back in February or so. I ended up scrapping it when life rendered it completely wrong almost as soon as I&amp;rsquo;d finished writing it. &amp;#x1f926;&#xA;Remember in part 3, where I mentioned that I got my windows replaced?&#xA;Apparently such investments have side-effects&amp;hellip;&#xA;Maybe I Should Start A Lemon Orchard &amp;hellip;Like frying the HVAC system, because it&amp;rsquo;s oversized for the house, when said house is properly insulated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Part 3</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/23/personal-finance-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/08/23/personal-finance-part-3/</guid>
      <description>In part 2, I mentioned that I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;productively lazy,&amp;rdquo; and prefer to automate what I can. Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve managed to do that with my finances.&#xA;Hello, Automation! My husband finally got officially hired by his work, which converted him to salary. This gave us two benefits &amp;ndash; 1. his income is no longer locked to his hours, so the paychecks are the same, and 2. he and I are now on the same pay schedule (which makes for a really pretty number on payday).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Finance, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/12/16/personal-finance-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/12/16/personal-finance-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Back in part 1 I described the system that I used to work on getting my family out of debt and make ends meet. We&amp;rsquo;re now coming up on a year, so how did I do? Does this system actually work?&#xA;Putting The System To Work So, did it work? Well, as an acquaintance put it, there was &amp;ldquo;no budge in the budget,&amp;rdquo; but&amp;hellip;yeah, it has been working. In fact, it saved our hides when things fell apart a few months ago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Personal Finance</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/04/getting-started-with-personal-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/04/04/getting-started-with-personal-finance/</guid>
      <description>I could have sworn I wrote earlier about how one of the things I was planning on doing was personal finance and money-making outside of a typical 9-5. Oh well, if I haven&amp;rsquo;t said it before, I&amp;rsquo;ll say it now &amp;ndash; I find it annoying that there seems to be a gap between &amp;ldquo;flat broke with zero personal finance knowledge&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;personal finance guru,&amp;rdquo; and I&amp;rsquo;d like to bridge that gap, while I&amp;rsquo;m crossing it.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
