<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I make stuff.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My profession is problem solving. My chosen tool by which to do that has been developing software. I&amp;rsquo;ve written shell scripts, maintained systems in .Net, built APIs in PHP, and implemented interfaces with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I&amp;rsquo;ve maintained legacy systems and built cutting-edge, life-changing applications, as well as created little tools to support other people in getting their work done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Writing software isn&amp;rsquo;t all I do, though. I like to write English words, too, and my writing is about as eclectic as my coding. While my blog started (ages ago) as a &amp;ldquo;tech and work blog,&amp;rdquo; it soon expanded out to other aspects of life, including personal finance and the broader culture. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll spin some topics off to their own blogs, eventually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/buy-me-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/buy-me-coffee/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;buy-me-coffee&#34;&gt;Buy Me Coffee&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Ways I Make Money From This Site)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-hate-ads&#34;&gt;I &lt;em&gt;Hate&lt;/em&gt; Ads&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do, with a passion. The first extension I install on any browser is AdBlock. That&amp;rsquo;s how much I hate them. I also hate when blogs write a &amp;ldquo;review&amp;rdquo; or other article for the sole purpose of selling that product. You know the kind I&amp;rsquo;m talking about. They read like a commercial and are full of keywords and buzzwords about the product. I can usually spot them a mile away and they annoy the crap out of me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/about/hire-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/about/hire-me/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;hiring-me&#34;&gt;Hiring Me&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking to work with me? Cool! Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the type of relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-type&#34;&gt;What Type?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;conventional-employment&#34;&gt;Conventional Employment&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you read through that &amp;#x261d;&amp;#xfe0f; and still want to hire me as a conventional employee? Well&amp;hellip;it didn&amp;rsquo;t scare you away, so that&amp;rsquo;s a start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For my sake and yours, I have a high bar for conventional employment in particular. Let&amp;rsquo;s put it this way: I&amp;rsquo;ve turned down Amazon roughly half a dozen times at this point.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
