<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Culture on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/culture/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Culture on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/culture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Companies are not family</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/27/companies-are-not-family/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/27/companies-are-not-family/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;re a family here!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;How many times have you heard that from your boss? Or perhaps even the CEO of your company? I&amp;rsquo;ve heard it at nearly every company I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for. And I&amp;rsquo;ve worked for a lot.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s A Trap (I considered the Star Wars meme, but I like this one better.)&#xA;What do you call a familial relationship in which one person controls another&amp;rsquo;s financial security in order to gain compliance?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What We Owe To Each Other</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</guid>
      <description>The topic of changing verbiage within the tech industry, particularly as it relates to references to &amp;ldquo;master,&amp;rdquo; particularly in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; contexts, but also in places like &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch in git (which does, in fact, have its roots in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; paradigm), came up in a couple of Slack groups in which I participate.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s certainly not new (some discussions on the matter date back a decade or more), but it&amp;rsquo;s always kind of a contentious topic when it comes up, despite the terminology getting phased out over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Core Values</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</guid>
      <description>As I&amp;rsquo;ve more actively sought out leadership positions, one of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about is the concept of core values. I see them actually communicated most often at the organization level, but I believe we have them at a personal level, too. We just don&amp;rsquo;t codify them. I like documenting things (because I like understanding), and since these are things I&amp;rsquo;d like to instill in the people I mentor and lead, I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be good to write them out and start documenting and exploring, and ultimately refining them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding One&#39;s Strengths</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s This Strengths Finding Thing? I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to a lot of podcasts lately. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly a fan of Smart Passive Income and Screw The Nine To Five. They&amp;rsquo;re both great podcasts for learning about how to build your own business in order to generate income that&amp;rsquo;s not dependent on trading your time for money. They&amp;rsquo;re a gold mine of various resources, not just for starting and running one&amp;rsquo;s own business, but for business and life stuff in general.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Culture Trumps Everything</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/15/when-culture-trumps-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/15/when-culture-trumps-everything/</guid>
      <description>I had an interesting experience recently.&#xA;I had a job opportunity dropped in my lap. A greenfield project that had a pay range $10-40k more than what I&amp;rsquo;m currently making.&#xA;You have my attention.&#xA;I responded to the recruiter and within a few days, I had an initial meeting/interview with one of the higher-ups at the company.&#xA;I went and had a nice conversation with him. He was a cool person, not much older than myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Exchange With Amazon On Workplace Culture</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/06/08/an-exchange-with-amazon-on-workplace-culture/</guid>
      <description>A couple of months ago, I got an invitation to an Amazon recruiting event:&#xA;Hi Shauna-&#xA;I came across your information in our system and your background is impressive! We are currently looking to hire Sr. Software Development Engineers (SDEs) to join the Amazon Retail team and are hosting an “Invitation Only” recruiting event for the Amazon Media and International Expansion (ISE) organizations specifically the week of February 16th.&#xA;If you’re interested in being considered for this opportunity, please reply with your updated resume to [Recruiter&amp;rsquo;s email] if you’d like to be considered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Open Letter To Recruiters</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/15/dear-recruiters/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2014/10/15/dear-recruiters/</guid>
      <description>Dear Third Party Recruiters,&#xA;Due to the high volume of contact requests I’ve received, I have decided to write this open letter in order to improve the quality of my network.&#xA;The Greater Columbus Area is home to a very large number of third party recruiting companies. This means you have a lot of competition. Competition should mean improved quality. Unfortunately, what I generally see is rather disappointing.&#xA;We tech folks are generally a merit-based people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
