<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Black Lives Matter on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/series/black-lives-matter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Black Lives Matter on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/series/black-lives-matter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What We Owe To Each Other</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/07/02/what-we-owe-to-each-other/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The topic of changing verbiage within the tech industry, particularly as it relates to references to &amp;ldquo;master,&amp;rdquo; particularly in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; contexts, but also in places like &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; branch in git (which does, in fact, &lt;a href=&#34;https://mail.gnome.org/archives/desktop-devel-list/2019-May/msg00066.html&#34;&gt;have its roots in the &amp;ldquo;master/slave&amp;rdquo; paradigm&lt;/a&gt;), came up in a couple of Slack groups in which I participate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s certainly not new (some discussions on the matter date back a decade or more), but it&amp;rsquo;s always kind of a contentious topic when it comes up, despite the terminology getting phased out over time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Riot Is the Language of the Unheard</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/06/11/a-riot-is-the-language-of-the-unheard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I attended a protest the other day. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d been downtown since it started and I had walked there (and back) from one of the suburbs. A nearly 5 mile walk each way, with the inner-most mile or two containing a lot of plywood covering up a lot of damage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But you know what stuck out to me? Two things:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Which places were hit.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Of the places that were damaged and thus boarded up, which had murals and which had graffiti.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These two things speak volumes about the situation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
