<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:02:55 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Blog Platform</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/15/new-blog-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 00:02:55 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/11/15/new-blog-platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So&amp;hellip;Pelican (my previous static site generator) took a dump on me when I went to upload my latest blog post&amp;hellip; I attempted multiple paths to resurrect it, but they&amp;rsquo;ve all ultimately failed. &amp;#x1f622;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a result, I&amp;rsquo;m moving my site to Hugo, but that requires some conversion (and probably clean-up). It&amp;rsquo;s been a bit tedious, but it does mean I&amp;rsquo;ve cleaned up my &lt;em&gt;ancient&lt;/em&gt; posts that are no longer relevant, which is a plus. It also means there might be some minor bugs or other things in need of tweaking, though, and possibly a couple of dead links. I think I got the important ones, but we&amp;rsquo;ll see.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github, Part 2</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 23:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github-part-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, I wrote a post on &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/&#34;&gt;automating the generation of my static-site blog&lt;/a&gt;. As they do, things have since changed, and I figured I&amp;rsquo;d update accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;changes-to-travis-and-travisyml&#34;&gt;Changes To Travis And .travis.yml&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Travis recently made several updates, many of which make our job easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;build-settings&#34;&gt;Build Settings&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Travis now has the option to build only if a .travis.yml file is present. Before, you needed a .travis.yml file in both your source and your display branch. Now, that&amp;rsquo;s no longer the case.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pelican, Travis, and Github</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/13/pelican-travis-and-github/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hey-o! There have been some changes made to this process. &lt;a href=&#34;http://shaunagordon.com/2017/09/01/pelican-travis-and-github&#34;&gt;Be sure to check out the updates.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is actually the second time I&amp;rsquo;ve leveraged &lt;a href=&#34;https://travis-ci.org/&#34;&gt;Travis CI&lt;/a&gt; for managing my static-site blog, but apparently I didn&amp;rsquo;t write about it. I had done it shortly after setting up the Octopress version of my blog. It was nice and convenient, and dramatically lowered the barrier to writing more blog entries, though I didn&amp;rsquo;t realize that until I lost that capability when I switched to Pelican (probably because the Octopress version was a bit finicky, due to breaking changes in the upstream Octopress repo, so the barrier was still pretty high).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
