<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal growth on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/personal-growth/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal growth on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/personal-growth/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year In Review</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2024/01/02/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Looks at dates on blog posts. Oh&amp;hellip;other than my Google Sheets thing, it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip;almost three years since I last posted&amp;hellip;&#xA;Oops. 😅&#xA;What have I been doing in that time? Well&amp;hellip;&#xA;Got A Job&amp;hellip;And Got Laid Off From Said Job In late 2021, I had a full time job opportunity fall into my lap. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a member of Gun.io since like&amp;hellip;2019 or something like that, back when I first started doing serious freelancing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Problem Solving</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/10/21/on-problem-solving/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/10/21/on-problem-solving/</guid>
      <description>The most important skill in tech isn&amp;rsquo;t the technology. It&amp;rsquo;s problem-solving. Whether you get into cyber security, system administration, or programming, the heart of all of it is really the ability to take a problem, break it apart, and work out a solution &amp;ndash; very often coming up with solutions that didn&amp;rsquo;t previously exist at all. Even on the more everyday scale, you&amp;rsquo;ll be constantly faced with error messages, odd software behavior, broken tests, and more that you&amp;rsquo;ll be expected to triage and if not fix yourself, hand off detailed information about the problem to those who can fix it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Core Values</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2018/03/08/personal-core-values/</guid>
      <description>As I&amp;rsquo;ve more actively sought out leadership positions, one of the things I&amp;rsquo;ve been thinking about is the concept of core values. I see them actually communicated most often at the organization level, but I believe we have them at a personal level, too. We just don&amp;rsquo;t codify them. I like documenting things (because I like understanding), and since these are things I&amp;rsquo;d like to instill in the people I mentor and lead, I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be good to write them out and start documenting and exploring, and ultimately refining them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finding One&#39;s Strengths</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2016/01/06/strengthsfinding/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s This Strengths Finding Thing? I&amp;rsquo;ve been listening to a lot of podcasts lately. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly a fan of Smart Passive Income and Screw The Nine To Five. They&amp;rsquo;re both great podcasts for learning about how to build your own business in order to generate income that&amp;rsquo;s not dependent on trading your time for money. They&amp;rsquo;re a gold mine of various resources, not just for starting and running one&amp;rsquo;s own business, but for business and life stuff in general.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
