<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>remote on I Make Things</title>
    <link>http://shaunagordon.com/tags/remote/</link>
    <description>Recent content in remote on I Make Things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://shaunagordon.com/tags/remote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Adventures In A Remote World</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/05/03/adventures-in-a-remote-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/05/03/adventures-in-a-remote-world/</guid>
      <description>Among my many blog post drafts, I have a satirical piece that was originally intended to turn all the &amp;ldquo;remote working is inferior [because it&amp;rsquo;s a new thing with a learning curve]&amp;rdquo; stuff on its head.
&amp;hellip;And then COVID-19 happened and pretty much overnight, just about everyone suddenly had to do at least some things remotely (even if work wasn&amp;rsquo;t one of them).
Schools are all now done in distance learning format (hat-tip to all of the school staff who busted their tails to make that pivot and get students of all ages going with relatively little disruption!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pandemic Work From Home Survival Guide</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/03/16/the-pandemic-work-from-home-survival-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2020/03/16/the-pandemic-work-from-home-survival-guide/</guid>
      <description>Some Notes:
Contrary to most of my other posts, I plan to update this one periodically as things change and this is still current. Check back periodically for updates.
Are you a business owner or manager? Have a look at Remotewave.io&amp;rsquo;s guide, which approaches it from your side. :)
Well&amp;hellip;now that half the world is in quarantine of some level, a great many people are suddenly finding themselves tossed head first in the deep end of remote working.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Defense Of Remote Friendly Work Environments</title>
      <link>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/05/15/in-defense-of-remote-friendly-work-environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://shaunagordon.com/2015/05/15/in-defense-of-remote-friendly-work-environments/</guid>
      <description>Since I posted my open letter to recruiters, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen a number of people speaking out against it (&amp;ldquo;against&amp;rdquo; used loosely here, ranging from &amp;ldquo;employees need to be in the office&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;the best companies hire the best people and the best people want to go into the office&amp;rdquo; (that&amp;rsquo;s not insulting at all) to &amp;ldquo;working remotely is isolating&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;in-person communication is better&amp;rdquo;). I decided to address a few of these things head-on.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
